Guide to the Department of Education, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Yale-Fairfield Study on elementary education, 1954-1960; Accession 1979-A-005
  - Inter-Office Correspondence (Miss Burns), 1954-1959 (Box 5)
  - Inter-Office Correspondence: General, 1954-1960 (Box 5)
  - Fellows Programs on Teaching: Reports, Evaluations, 1954-1960 (Box 6)
  - Printed Matter re: Various Subjects on Teaching Concepts, 1954-1960 (Box 6)
  - Mostly Forms, Printed Matter and Evaluations of Teachers, 1954-1960 (Box 6)
- Records concerning the Post-Doctoral Seminar in Education, 1954-1982; Accession 1992-A-043
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2018
  - Memorandum which instituted post-doctoral seminar in education, 1954? (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Post-Doctoral Seminars
    - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Post-doctoral directory responses (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mailing list, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Education Department and Master of Arts in Teaching Program reunion packet and audiocassettes, 1991; Accession 1999-A-047 (Box 1)